export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "52 + 32 =?",
            "answers": ["84", "80", "78", "82"],
            "correctAnswer": "84"
          },
          {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "40 + 17 =?",
            "answers": ["55", "53", "57", "51"],
            "correctAnswer": "57"
          },
          {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "13 + 8 =?",
            "answers": ["18", "16", "20", "21"],
            "correctAnswer": "21"
          },
          {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "8 + 5 =?",
            "answers": ["12", "11", "10", "13"],
            "correctAnswer": "13"
          },
          {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "29 + 21 =?",
            "answers": ["48", "47", "49", "50"],
            "correctAnswer": "50"
          },
          {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "25 + 14 =?",
            "answers": ["36", "37", "38", "39"],
            "correctAnswer": "39"
          },
          {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "15 + 6 =?",
            "answers": ["19", "18", "21", "20"],
            "correctAnswer": "21"
          },
          {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "15 + 9 =?",
            "answers": ["22", "21", "24", "23"],
            "correctAnswer": "24"
          },
          {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "25 + 16 =?",
            "answers": ["39", "38", "41", "40"],
            "correctAnswer": "41"
          },
          {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "12 + 8 =?",
            "answers": ["17", "18", "19", "20"],
            "correctAnswer": "20"
          }
    ],
  };
  